Kira Kosuke, age fourteen.
Ran away from home and his abusive father.
Started with pickpocketing and larceny,
ended up killing, then raping, three women.
Killing then raping?
Isn't it the other way?
No, the report's right.
He looks cute, but he's a psycho.
Age fourteen, huh?
This is gonna be a big deal.
I just heard that Natsume Soichi's going to be his lawyer.
Natsume?
That over-compassionate hotshot?
He supposedly talked the dad into letting him.
Bastard just wants the attention.
That'll be one hell of a trial.
Depending on the psych eval, he may not be in long at all.
Hell if I care.
Thanks to the laws protecting minors,
we can't do a thing.
Hey.
What is it?
That little bastard...
He's grinning.
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
This is where tomorrow brings a new game
It's time to learn that pain is gain
Ready fight
To squash my past despair
kako no shitsubou nuritsubusu tame ni
I've had to sacrifice my future
gisei ni shite kita mirai
Until my life expires
boku no life ga tsukiru made
I'll keep fighting my fate
sono sadame buchikowashiteiku no sa
Ah, break out and start a revolution
Searching for the exact answer
hitotsu no kotae wo sagashite
I challenge myself to an extreme race
genkai no race ni idonde
I know it's my only chance
ichidokiri no chansu to shitte
I'll overcome my preordained fate
seotta unmei koeteikun da yo
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
the game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
Day 2: Noon
Ninety-five...
Ninety-six.
So you were here?
Ninety-seven.
What are you doing?
Ninety-eight.
Ninety-nine.
One hundred!
Oh, Natsume.
These frogs are all over the place.
Best in the World
Pretty gross, huh?
What's wrong with killing living things?
Don't you feel sorry for them?
No matter how small they are, they're still alive.
Feel sorry? Why would I?
Humans kill pigs and cows to eat,
but we're supposed to feel bad about a few frogs?
Killing something to eat and doing it for pure amusement are two very different things.
I know that!
I'm not exactly stupid.
What I want to know is, if nobody cares, why can't I?
Anyway, what's wrong is wrong!
You said you're not stupid, so shouldn't you know that?
That again?!
You grown-ups always get bored halfway
through your explanations and give up.
We saw that yesterday.
They're doing drops at regular intervals.
It could be supplies or something.
I'm gonna check it out.
Hold on.
We don't know what will happen.
Let's bring your father too.
Honestly...
You don't mind talking back to me,
but the minute your father comes up, you don't say a word.
That attitude of yours is what makes him so violent.
You should show him how you feel.
Oh, there it is.
I wonder what's inside.
It'll be a little difficult to get up there.
Hey, Kosuke.
Gimme a bomb.
But...
Your ones are better suited for this.
This how you use it?
Hey, what's going on?!
Let me take a look.
It isn't working.
Seems only their owner can trigger them.
Kosuke, you do it.
Get on it, already!
Sir, you're just scaring him.
Shut up already!
If you would.
It worked.
I-It's dangerous, get back.
Let's see what we've got here!
Hell, yeah!
Instant ramen, canned food, a flashlight, and even beer!
This is amazing.
Okay.
Anyone who wants to eat, follow me.
M-Mr. Kira...
That belongs to all of us.
We should divide it between us right here!
What're you talking about?
This was my idea, and my son got it.
You had nothing to do with it.
B-But...
Listen up.
Out here, there ain't no rules and ain't no police.
It don't matter squat if you're a lawyer.
Here, you're just a useless mouth to feed.
The strong rule the weak.
That's the law of the jungle.
Got a problem with that?
S-Scum...
You say something?
You gonna talk back to me? Huh?!
Looks like you need some special attention.
Want me to help you remember?
"Achievement Unlocked:
Forty Hours of Continuous Play."
You skipped school to play that game again?!
Don't show-up your parents like this!
Who do you think feeds you?
Huh?!
Wh-What the hell did you do?
Mr. Kira!
Your shirt! Take off your shirt!
Wait!
Kosuke! You—
Look, Natsume!
I did it! I showed him how I felt, just like you told me to!
That's the first time I've ever fought back!
Natsume, you'll protect me again, right?
I mean, I'm insane, right?
Because I was abused, right?
Because...
I just killed him, and I...
I feel wonderful!
It's your fault, Dad.
You didn't give me a choice.
Right?
You'll be my lawyer again, right?
You'll tell everyone at the trial, right?
I can't take this anymore.
I can't take this anymore!
I never should've agreed to be your lawyer!
Y-You're human garbage.
You're defective, raised wrong!
The father was bad, but his son's even worse!
I hope you stay on this island forever!
What?
You said you'd protect me.
Liar.
Radar?
What?
What's going on?
And how can someone be here without showing up on sonar?
I get it.
It's just like BTOOOM!'s system.
Sonar only locates people who are moving.
That's what happened this morning.
I wasn't moving, so she didn't see me.
And it happened to me this time, huh?
That corpse doesn't look like
the result of an explosion.
What did he do?
Did you kill him?
He deserved to die.
Was I wrong?
There's no police or rules here.
Lawyers are just mouths to feed.
It's survival of the fittest.
The strong rule the weak.
That's the law of the jungle.
If you don't do what I say,
you'll end up like him.
Hey, listen.
Calm down, and hear me out.
You're telling me what to do?!
When someone doesn't listen to
what you tell them to do...
...they need special attention, right?
This is dangerous.
Let's run.
Dad, I'm taking your BIMs and the food.
That's gross, Dad!
Now!
Running won't help you.
Because this world...
is just like BTOOOM!, and I'm super-good at it!
I won't let you get away.
He used his sonar.
Is he going to follow us?
What do we do?
Keep running like this?
Or...
No!
I can't kill any more people!
Mr. Taira!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just tripped a little.
Ow!
Crap...
Go on ahead.
Leave me here.
If you leave me, you'll survive.
Get going.
Taira can't run.
I have to do something.
But... do I really have to risk my own life
for some old guy I just met?
I...
Mr. Taira, hide here.
If you don't move, he'll never find you.
What are you going to do?
I'll draw him away.
You can run while I do.
You're going to fight him?!
S-Sakamoto!
I can do this!
I'll teach him a lesson, take his BIMs,
and that'll be the end of this.
Damn it!
I can do this.
I'm one of the best BTOOOM! players in the world.
He's coming.
About fifty meters away?
I won't be able to judge distances
that well until I get used to it.
He used his sonar.
He's after the case.
I won't let him have it!
He used it again.
I'm confident that I won't lose to any adults here.
I'll show you who's the strongest,
and who has to listen to who.
Again...
That brat, he's carefully judging the distance
between us and getting closer.
He knows how to use his radar.
The kid has two types of BIMs.
We're on equal terms.
What kind of BIMs does he have?
Timers?
Crackers?
Or...
He's close!
This is bad.
I need to get farther away.
No...
I need...
to get closer!
Did I get him?
He's okay?
The kid and I were thinking the same thing?
And he used the BIM on landing, a suggested tactic?
That settles it...
He's a BTOOOM! player.
And with a three-star rank.
But I'm a four-star player!
He's a BTOOOM! player.
Standard tactics won't
work on either of us.
What's going on?
This is fun!
It's so much fun!
We collect these, huh?
Sakamoto, don't die, okay?
I'm waiting for you.
He has cracker BIMs.
What's the other type?
What's up?
Not gonna fight back?
You scared already?
I have to think before I attack.
I need to set a trap.
This is boring. You're just running.
Don't disappoint me, okay?
You think a lame-ass trap
like that will beat me?
That wasn't the real attack.
He'll attack...
from the front!
It won't be that easy!
Bullseye!
Stay away!
An implosion type?!
That would've killed me.
Completely...
You're a BTOOOM! player, right?
So come on, fight me for real.
You're pretty good at the game, aren't you?
We both know it.
You don't plan on killing me, do you?
You think you can settle this without killing me.
I can tell how naïve you are.
I can tell a lot of things.
You're pretty good at the game,
but I bet you suck at real life.
You're a stupid kid.
I bet you never leave your room!
The way to do it is just to think of one like the other.
Live real life like a game!
We're so strong 'cause we treat the game like our life, right?
We beat everyone else, right?
Your problem is that you hold back in real life.
Live life boldly, just like a game!
Shut up!
You're just a kid who can't tell the two apart.
Quit talking like you actually know something!
There?
If you want to say something, show yourself first.
Talking big while you hide...
Sure sounds like an online gamer.
Maybe you really are NEET!
Shut up!
Feel like fighting now?
Crackers and timers, huh?
I see.
What is this?
A dream?
Just now, was I playing the game in my room?
That's right...
It's a game.
It isn't real.
This whole setup smells like bull.
I can prove it, too.
The flames aren't even hot.
But strangely, my senses are really sharp.
Yeah.
It's the feeling I always have.
Like I'm watching myself from behind.
A feeling that belongs to me alone.
There he is!
What's he thinking?
You're wide open!
Get him!
What was that?
An empty pouch?
No way, awesome!
That's what I'm talking about!
I'm running low on BIMs, too.
I'll finish this with the next one.
No response?
You stopped moving, huh?
But you know, I can tell you're hiding there.
A trick like that can't fool me.
It burns! It burns!
He's serious!
He was going to kill me.
What happened?
Nothing?
He never stopped back there.
He kept moving!
But then why... Why didn't the sonar work?
The sonar's working fine.
I-It can't be...
Finally figured it out, huh?
That's right.
Radar canceling.
You have a habit of firing your
sonar every time you use a BIM.
If I use mine at the same time, I can cancel it out...
and you can't see me.
I can read your mind!
I still can't see him?
Ridiculous!
He can't be canceling me every time!
No one's that pro.
Am I imagining it?
Is he just hiding somewhere?
If he's really radar canceling, where is he?!
Is he moving?
Is he hiding?
I've got no idea!
Got you!
I won.
Of course I did.
I'm one of the best players in the world.
I...
This is real!
I-It's not a game.
I was just about...
to kill someone again?
We lost each other that day
ano hi kara katamuita
You're in another time and space
jikan jikuu no dokoka ni kimi wa ite
Even if I reach out my fingers
doko made mo yubi no saki
I can only feel the breeze
nobashita kedo kaze shika tsukamenai
Day and night, I feel so guilty
asa mo yoru mo kokoro ga
For the wrong choices I've made
semeru no yo naze doushite
Now I just need some
ato sukoshi jibun sae
Trust in myself
shinjitara
Can't go away
can't go away
I'm cowering away again
dame da to mata nigeteru
I need to face reality
mitsumerunda riaru wo
I can't believe you totally had me figured out.
You're amazing.
A genius.
I can do without...
your compliments.
I'm taking your BIMs and the trunk.
Don't blame me.
I left you something to eat.
Take it.
You gonna tell me your name before you go?
It's Sakamoto.
Sakamoto, huh?
I'll never forget it.
Sakamoto...
No way!
The only Japanese player in the top-ten?
That Sakamoto?
Wow!
This island rocks!
Someone we knew sent us to this island.
They wanted us to disappear.
Our own society abandoned us.
Not just us...
Attack
Episode
everyone on this island.